# **SWAPNIL KANSARA**

# Digital Marketing and Creative

+91-9173899076 @ swapnilkansara6@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

I have 4 years of experience in marketing, as well as strong leadership skills and a track record of success. I'm currently looking for a position that will allow me to use my extensive skills and experience to find new clients and develop online strategies that will help businesses grow.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Sales Associate

iPearl Store (Authorized Apple reseller)

**=** 07/2018 - 10/2020

- · Selling electronic products of Apple brand
- Troubleshooting and technical support to existing customer for their existing Apple devices store merchandise by using creative skills to boost sales of targeted products.

### Sales Executive

Axis Bank (On payroll of Quess Corp. Ltd.)

**=** 01/2021 - 05/2022

- Selling and marketing of POS machines for Axis Bank in Ahmedabad territory through lead generation.
- · B2B sales, end to end marketing.
- Also selling other banking products such as Insurance, Bank savings & Current accounts.

# Jr. Channel Development and Sales Executive

Amity Infosoft Pvt. Ltd.

**=** 06/2022 - 11/2022

- Developing sales and marketing stratergies to drive sales growth in the assigned area.
- Develop and manage an efficient distribution network to improve sales performance.
- . Manage the sales team for sales growth and revenue enhancement conduct market research to understand competitions and market trends.
- Provide innovative ideas and suggestions to improve the market presence.

## Sales Executive

Flying Lion Media Pvt. Ltd.

苗 11/2022 - Present

- Launching optimized online advertisement to increase company and brand awareness.
- Developing sales and marketing stratergies to drive sales growth at digital platform
- Develop and manage an efficient distribution network to improve sales performance.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Grade 10th

Lok Niketan school

**=** 04/2015 - 03/2016

Grade 12TH

#### Bachelore in Arts

R.H Patel Arts & Commerce College

**=** 09/2020 - 05/2023

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

### iPearl Store

Consistent top performer (highest revenue sales) for consecutive 4 months in 2019.

## Axis Bank

Received appereciation for selling highest number of POS machine in a day.